(巨人) (海盗) (…)
(巴特侠) ↗
把那噪音关掉!
Turn that noise off!
我叫你把那音乐关掉!
I thought I told you to turn that thing off!
大晚上的, 还那么大声
It's too late, and it's too loud.
但是老爸, 我刚听到最精彩的地方
But dad, this is the best part.
不要再给我把时间浪费在这垃圾音乐上
You are wasting your time with this garbage,
马上滚去睡觉!
Now, Go to bed!
(迈克尔杰克逊海报)
算你狠, 既然如此…
Okay…
(报纸头条: 我被UFO绑架了)
(音频输入)
(开)
(大音量)
(更大音量)
(你疯了么!?!)
尝尝这个!
Eat this!
恐怕你爸回来的时候会被你气死
I'm afraid your father is going to be very upset when he gets back.
(正片开始)
嗷!
Aw!
啊--!
Ah--!
嗷!
Aw!
我带着宝贝在周末开车兜风
I took my baby on a Saturday bang.
人问「小伙子, 这是你的姑娘吗?」
Boy, is that girl with you?
我答「是的, 我们心心相印, 合二为一」
Yes, we're one and the same.
现在我相信奇迹
Now I believe in miracles,
而今夜奇迹已经显现
And a miracle has happened tonight!
唔!
Woo!
但, 如果, 你在意我的姑娘
But, if, you're thinkin' about my baby,
你是黑是白, 我都不在意
It don't matter if you're black or white.
哦!
Oh!
他们把我的消息刊登到《周末太阳报》上
They print my message in the Saturday Sun.
我得告诉他们, 我不比谁差
I had to tell them I ain't second to none.
我坚信人人平等
And I told about equality,
无论你是对是错, 都改变不了这个真理
And it's true either you're wrong or you're right!
唔!
Woo!
但, 如果, 你在意我的姑娘
But, if, you're thinkin' about my baby,
你是黑是白, 我都不在意
It don't matter if you're black or white.
唔!
Woo!
Go! Da bet!
唔~ 嘿!
Woo~ hey!
我受够这种谬误!
I'm tired of this devil!
我受够这些套路!
I'm tired of this stuff!
我受够这堆破事!
I'm tired of this business!
直到亡羊才去补牢
Sew when the going gets rough…
我不怕你的哥们! (隐喻3K党)
I ain't scared of your brother!
我不怕那白床单! (隐喻3K党)
I ain't scared of no sheets!
我天不怕地不怕!
I ain't scared of nobody!
宝贝! 只要有意义…
Girl! When the goin' gets mean…
啊--!
Ah--!
嗷!
Aw!
帮派, 社团, 民族各自为政
Protection.
For gangs clubs and nations.
使人际关系不断受创
Causing grief in human relations.
这是世界级的地域大战
It's a turf war, on a global scale.
我宁可兼听双方
I'd rather hear both sides of the tale.
不关乎种族
See, it's not about races,
只关乎面孔
Just places, faces.
与你的血缘
Where your blood comes from… this places.
我看到光明正在暗淡
I've seen the bright get duller.
我这辈子不是为了某种肤色而活
I'm not gonna spend my life being a color.
当你还在我面前恶意中伤
Don't tell me you agree with me,
就不要说你同意我的言论
When I saw you kicking dirt in my eye!
唔~ 嘿!
Woo~ hey!
但, 如果, 你在意我的姑娘
But, if, you're thinkin' about my baby,
你是黑是白, 我都不在意
It don't matter if you're black or white.
我是说, 如果你想成为我的宝贝
I, said, if you're thinkin' of being my baby,
你是黑是白, 我都不在意
It don't matter if you're black or white.
我是说, 如果你想成为我的兄弟
I, said, if you're thinkin' of being my brother,
你是黑是白, 我都不在意
It don't matter if you're black or white.
好了
Alright.
啊,
Ah,
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
唔!
Woo!
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑…
It's black…
就是这样!
Alright!
啊,
Ah,
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
唔!
Woo!
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑…
It's black…
就是这样!
Alright!
啊,
Ah,
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
唔!
Woo!
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
只要你要强, 你便是强者
It's tough for you to be bad… Yeah, yeah, yeah…
是黑, 是白
It's black, it's white,
唔!
Woo!
卡! 完美! …
Cut! That's perfect! …
(「黑豹之舞」片段开始)
(玻璃: 希特勒万岁)
(玻璃: 黑鬼滚回家去)
(玻璃: 抵制墨西哥移民)
(玻璃: 3K党)
(招牌: 皇家酒店)
…嗷!
…Aw!
巴特! 把那噪音关了
Bart! Turn off that noise.
嗷!
Aw!
(偏见即是无知)